EU
I've already stepped on shit
I stepped in shit here bro
oha
Dude is so messy bro
if you had 1200
I tell you what I would do to set up 1 business in 22 days
I think this 8th EU day
ah tô 1 little tired
draws
if i don't have that energy to bring that disposition
for sale
people feel dear
and then the sale does not flow
is on
I know it's too risky
but i think today
I'm going to rest Man
I know I'm going to miss 1 day of sale
at a time that is important to me now
rest
I'm in the dark
ah I stepped on shit
this is real life
and then I said I was going to set up a business
if i sell on the street i won't set up 1 deal
I will make money
I need to think of some idea to put something together
know if to stop 1 little
earn money in a bigger way to be able to climb
that if we stay that way all the time it won't happen
brother i need to figure out how to do passive lace man
I'm going to call some friend who understands business
to power
give me a light
know i'm creative
but i think this one-on-one sale
I won't be able to scale the deal
I'm going to call my friend to see what he thinks
and there Fish
how are you brother
I'm fine Cara
I'm in a
entrenched
needed your help Cara
I have 1,200 reals more OR less
I have 22 days to be able to set up 1 business
twenty-two days and one thousand two hundred reais
the same is pure Resso guy
however
your plan is ok
I will do this
but then man
what would i suggest
so you get yours to a day to day one on the street
and take it digital
your brother you agree with me saw you too bro
hug is that
now i need to think about passive lace bro
if i have to use the lighting
and take her to another level
so it turns on in the next few episodes
tamo together valeu